*** your 30s and living in New York,
孩子们 等你们到了30岁还住在纽约
there's a few places you just never want to be:
有几个地方你们绝对不会想去
Times Square on New Year's Eve,
新年夜的时代广场
Rockefeller Center around Christmastime...
圣诞节前后的洛克菲勒中心
but most of all... A college bar? Oh,man.
但是你们最不想去的地方应该是 大学酒吧? 有没有搞错
We're probably going to run into my students.
我们可能会遇上我的学生
They're going to corner me and want a free lecture.
他们会围上来 让我给他们免费讲一课
I don't even have my slide projector. Damn it.
我都没带幻灯机 他妈的
Ted,I've been Skee-Ball champ here since law school.
Ted我上法学院开始 就是这里的滑雪球冠军
I have to pop in at least once a month to maintain my record.
我必须一个月至少来一次 来保持我的记录
Whoa. Looks like you've been gone a while.
哇 看起来你好久没来了
Some guy named Big Fudge has been cleaning up.
这个叫大软糖的人已经接你的班了
Yeah,he has.
是啊
- And you're Big Fudge. - The biggest.
- 你是大软糖? - 正是在下
- Um,so by the way,I-I have to tell you something. - Yeah.
- 另外我有事要告诉你 - 啥事
I,uh... invited Jenkins.
我邀请了Jenkins
Jenkins? No way!
Jenkins?不会吧?
We'd all started hearing about Jenkins a few weeks earlier.
我们几个星期之前 就已经开始听说Jenkins了
You guys will not believe what Jenkins did this time.
你们肯定不会相信 这次Jenkins做了什么
Who's Jenkins?
谁是Jenkins?
Oh,he's this hilarious new lawyer at Marshall's office.
他是Marshall办公室新来的 超级搞笑的律师
Hilarious.
超级搞笑
Okay,so there's this jar of Maraschino cherries in the fridge at work.
好吧 今天办公室冰箱里 有一瓶黑樱桃果酱
So,Jenkins says,"200 bucks,I'll eat the whole jar.
Jenkins说 给我200块钱 我就整瓶吃掉
" So,we give Jenkins 200 bucks...
然后我们给了Jenkins200块钱
...and Jenkins ate the whole jar!
Jenkins整瓶吃掉了
Jenkins.
Jenkins
And after that,the stories kept coming.
这之后 故事持续不断
So,the CFO comes in to sign some acquisition papers.
财务总监进来签署收购文件
So,Jenkins goes,"Excuse me,Mr. Wilcox.
Jenkins就说 不好意思 Wilcox先生
I think we forgot one of the documents.
我们忘了一份文件
" Jenkins!
Jenkins
So,we all go out for beers after work.
我们下了班去喝啤酒
Jenkins gets up on the bar and starts gyrating
Jenkins爬上桌子开始扭
like some sort of deranged stripper.
跟个发疯的脱衣舞女似的
Next thing you know,off comes the shirt!
还没等你反应过来  衬衫已经脱下来了
It was so gross.
太恶心了
Jenkins.
Jenkins
Right?
是吧
Well,it'll be great to finally meet the famous Jenkins
听到这些故事以后能亲眼见到
after all those stories.
这位著名的Jenkins真是太好了
Yeah. And there's about to be one more story.
是啊 接下来还有个故事
I'm going to bang Jenkins.
我要上Jenkins
- What? - You heard me.
- 什么? - 我说真的
You-you want to have sex with Jenkins?
你想和Jenkins发生性关系?
With Jenkins,on Jenkins,near Jenkins. You name it.
上床 睡觉 性关系 随便你怎么说吧
I want to wear Jenkins like a sock.
我想和Jenkins爽个透
You... but you're...
但是你...你是...
Haven't you...
你不是...
I'm... Really?
我...你说真的?
Hey,guys.
各位好
Ted,this is Jenkins.
Ted 这是Jenkins
Okay,this is going to sound crazy,but I thought Jenkins was a guy.
可能会听起来有点疯狂 我以为Jenkins是个男的
What? That's crazy! What gave you that idea?
什么? 你疯了 你为什么会这么以为
Oh,I don't know. Maybe the whole "Jenkins peed out the window of a cab" story.
我不知道 可能是那个"Jenkins 从出租车窗口往外尿尿"的故事
Yeah. Much more impressive now,isn't it?
是啊 现在觉得很惊人了吧
Yeah.
是啊
Okay,I'll come clean!
好吧 我坦白
It all started a few weeks ago.
都是几个星期前开始的
By the way,Four Eyes,new lawyer. This is Jenkins.
另外 四眼儿 新来了个律师 这是Jenkins
Watch out for this guy. He steals stuff.
小心这个家伙 他偷东西
I don't steal stuff.
我不偷东西
And I don't wear glasses.
我也不戴眼镜
- I'm Marshall. - Hi,Marshall.
- 我是Marshall. - 嗨 Marshall.
So,are you really a Vikings fan or was he lying about that,too?
你真的是维京人队的粉丝 还是他又是在撒谎?
Why? Is this a trap? Are you a Packers fan?
为什么?是个陷阱吗? 你是包装工队的粉丝吗?
My wife knows I'm here.
我老婆知道我在这里
She doesn't have money,but what she does have
她虽然没有钱 但是她却
is a very special set of skills.
拥有一系列特殊技能
I'm a Vikings fan,too!
我也是维京人队的粉丝
I bleed purple and gold. I'm from Pelican Rapids.
我超爱紫色和金色的(维京队徽颜色) 我来自Pelican Rapids
- Pelican Rapids? No way. - Yeah.
- Pelican Rapids? 不是吧 - 是
My grandpa lives in Pelican Rapids.
我爷爷住在Pelican Rapids
Well,I mean,he's dead now,but he haunts a barn off Route 108.
他现在已经死了 但是他的魂儿经常 游荡在108公路上的一个谷仓附近
Whoa! Hold it,hold it.
哇哦 等一下 等一下
Dude,if you tell me you have a thing for a woman that is not your wife,
伙计 你要是敢说你对一个 不是你妻子的女人有感觉
I will drag you outside and kick your ass.
我就把你拖出去痛打你一顿
Okay,first of all...
好了 首先
come on,buddy. You can't handle the Fudge.
伙计 你根本对付不了大软糖
Second of all,no. I think of her like a... a big brother.
其次 我只是把她当成一个哥们看待
Who,I guess,has boobs.
一个有胸脯的哥哥
But so does my oldest brother,Marvin Jr.
但是我大哥也有胸 Marvin Jr.
Anyway,that night,I told Lily about it.
总之 那天晚上 我告诉Lily
Jenkins.
Jenkins
I can't wait to meet him.
我真想见见他
I should have corrected her.
我当时应该纠正她
It would have been so easy.
当时应该很容易
But I didn't,so,after that,
但是我没有 从那以后
whenever I talked about Jenkins,I always avoided pronouns.
每次我说到Jenkins  我总是避免用人称代词
So,the head of marketing comes in to choose people for the Midwest audit.
市场部的头头过来选人 做中西部的审计
So,he goes,"Him,him,her,"him,him...
他说 他 他 她 他 他
Jenkins,him,her.
Jenkins 他 她
" Look,I don't understand why you wouldn't just tell Lily.
听着 我不明白 你为什么不直接告诉Lily
Do you really think she'd be all that jealous?
你真的认为她会嫉妒
Ted,think about those stories I told you.
Ted想一想我告诉你的那些故事
Yeah,I could see how that'd be a problem.
是啊 我明白为什么会有问题了
Exactly. That's why Lily can't find out.
就是 这就是为什么不能让Lily知道
Lily can't find out what?
不能让Lily知道什么
That Marshall's going to buy her a horse.
Marshall要给她买匹马
You are? That is so awesome! I love those things.
真的?太好了 我超爱马的
Hey,guys,why... why is that kid over there staring at me?
各位 为什么那边有个孩子一直盯着我
I think I know what this is.
我想我知道原因了
I think it has finally happened.
我想这件事终于发生了
I'm getting recognized from my show.
人们看了我的节目开始认出我来了
Oh,Robin,that is so cute.
哦 Robin 太好了
But that's Scotty. He's one of my students,and he's looking at me.
不过那是Scotty 他是我的学生 他是在看我
How weird is it that I'm more famous than you?
多奇怪啊 我比你出名
Not at all,'cause you're not. I'm on TV.
一点也不奇怪 因为你不我出名 我出现在电视上
Yeah,and I have 30 students in my class.
是啊 我班上有30个学生
That's what,30 times your viewership?
是你的观众数量的三十倍
Now,this will give Scotty a little thrill--
我们来让Scotty小小激动一下吧
buying a drink for the old prof.
来给教授敬杯酒
All right,Scotter,one question about neoclassical architecture, and that is it.
好吧 Scotty  只许问一个关于古典建筑的问题
You're Robin Scherbatsky,right?
你是Robin Scherbatsky 对吧?
- What? - Yes,I am.
- 什么? - 我是
Wow. Look,I-I didn't mean to stare.
哇 我不是故意要盯着你
It's just,I watch your show all the time.
我一直看你的节目
- Really? - Really?
- 真的? - 真的?
Totally.
千真万确
What are you doing out with Ted?
你怎么和Ted在一起
- Uh,it's Professor Mosby. - We're friends.
- 我是Mosby教授 - 我们是朋友
Holy crap!
我靠来
Robin Scherbatsky is friends with my econ professor.
Robin Scherbatsky和我的 经济学教授是朋友
It's architecture! All right,you know what,Scotty? You're crowding us. Hit the bricks.
是建筑学 好了 Scotty 别来烦我们了 哪凉快去哪儿吧
Wait a minute. You're Big Fudge.
等一下 你是大软糖
Go!
快滚
- Hello? - Hey,baby,I'm on my way up.
- 你好? - 嘿 宝贝 我在来你这里的路上
What? Why?
什么? 为什么?
There was a measles outbreak at school,and they called a half day.
学校里爆发麻疹 然后他们放了半天假
S Thought I'd come by here,have lunch,maybe give you the measles.
我就想过来跟你一起吃午饭 或者顺便把麻疹传染给你
Okay.
好吧
Um,I have a problem. That was my wife.
我有问题了 刚才是我老婆
When I first mentioned you,s he mistakenly thought you were a guy,and so...
我第一次向她提起你的时候 她误以为你是个男的
So,now you're worried that when she finds out I'm a woman,
现在你担心如果她发现我是个女人
she's going to totally flip out.
她会彻底抓狂
Yes. E-exactly.
是的 确实
Oh,geez. Oh,gosh. Okay. Okay,I was in an improv group in Pelican Rapids. Follow my lead.
哦天啊 我在Pelican Rapids 进过即兴表演小组 照我的做
Okay.
好吧
Hey,baby.
嘿 宝贝
I'm Lily,Marshall's wife.
我是Lily Marshall的妻子
Hi,Lily. I am from the French embassy.
嗨 Lily 我是法国大使馆的
I am here because of a small but significant cheese incident that occurred...
我来是因为这里发生了一起很小 但是很严重的奶酪事故...
She's Jenkins!
她是Jenkins
You're Jenkins?
你是Jenkins?
Yeah,well,that,uh,Camembert cris isn't going to resolve itself,
恩 是啊 奶酪事故还有待解决
so I'll catch you guys on the flip-flop.
那我们就等会儿再见
Marshall cringed. This was the moment he had feared.
Marshall害怕了 这就是他惊恐的时刻
The famous Jenkins! How about that?
著名的Jenkins 真有意思
Funny,I was picturing a guy. Anywho,lunch?
好玩 我还以为是个男的 谁想吃午餐?
Wait. W-w-wait. So... so,you're not jealous at all?
等一下 你一点也不嫉妒?
Oh,sweetie.
哦 宝贝
I never have to worry about you with another woman.
我永远也用不着担心你和另一个女人
Right,because we're so hopelessly in love,right?
对 因为我们爱的死去活来是吧
Yeah,sure. Anywho,lunch?
是啊 当然 谁想吃午餐?
She wasn't jealous at all.
她一点也不嫉妒
Of course,she wasn't jealous.
当然她不会嫉妒
That's the whole dynamic of your relationship.
这是你们关系中的局势
What's that supposed to mean?
你这是什么意思
Uh,it's like this,my man.
听我给你讲 哥们
Every good relationship has a reacher and a settler.
每个良好的关系 有一个高攀者和一个屈就者
Exactly. One person reaches for someone out of their league;
正是 一个人高攀上一个比自己好的人
the other one settles for someone below theirs.
另外一个屈就给不如自己的一个人
I did not settle for Lily.
我没有屈就给Lily
Okay,yes,she's a little short,and--
虽然她确实有点儿矮
true - my mom says she doesn't have the hips to birth an Eriksen child,but...
而且我妈妈说屁股太小不能生孩子
Oh,my God,you guys think I'm the reacher.
哦 天啊 你们认为我是高攀者
That's why Lily's not jealous.
这就是为什么Lily一点也不嫉妒
The settler is never jealous of the reacher because,
屈就者从来不会因为高攀者嫉妒
where is the reacher going to go?
因为高攀者还能如何啊
The settler,Lily,is the best thing that the reacher,
屈就者Lily是高攀者Marshall
Marshall,is ever going to get.
所能配的上到的最好的人了
No. No... okay.
不 不 好吧
Yes,I am lucky to have Lily,but Lily is just as lucky...
我很幸运能和Lily在一起 但是Lily也同样幸运
to have me.
能和我在一起
Okay. Neither one of us is the reacher.
我们俩没人是高攀者
Dude,you are so the reacher. You're getting her a horse!
伙计 你完全就是高攀者 你都要给她买匹马了
- What? - Shh. Take the hit. Take the hit.
- 什么? - 嘘 别反抗了 别反抗了
Thus ending modern architecture's very brief experiment
关于V型结构的现代建筑学的简短实验
with the V-frame house.
就到此结束了
Um... Excuse me a second.
恩...稍等一下
- What are you doing here? - I noticed you forgot something this morning,
- 你来干嘛? - 你今天早上落东西了
so I thought I'd bring it by. Your pen.
所以我想我给你捎过来吧 你的钢笔
This is your pen. And you chewed on the end of it. Recently.
这是你的钢笔 你还咬过钢笔头 刚咬的
Ah,not a problem,Ted.
不客气 Ted
- Your class was on my way to work. - No,it's not.
- 我上班刚好路过 - 你不路过
AtCome On,Get Up New York! ,where I'm an anchor,so...
我节目是 醒来吧纽约 我是主播
I watch your show all the time.
我一直都看你的节目
What?! You watch the show?
什么?!你看我的节目?
Oh! Well,paint me flattered. Any other fans out there?
哦 好吧 我很荣幸 还有谁是我的粉丝吗
- Oh,we got... oh. - Okay,all right. Thanks for coming by,Robin.
- 哦 这位...哦 - 好了 谢谢你过来 Robin
Oh,well,tune in tonight. I am doing a great piece on snail poison.
今晚注意收看 我今晚做一期很棒的 关于食用蜗牛中毒节目
Also,who's got the worst pizza in New York?
另外纽约哪家家的披萨最烂
I'll give you the answer after traffic on the ones,threes,fives and nines.
路况信息后我会给你们答案
Really? You guys watch her show?
当真? 你们看她的节目?
It's like watching a well-lit aquarium,but not as interesting.
感觉就像看一个光线充足的水箱 但是没水箱那么有意思
And now that I think about it,not as well lit.
仔细想想 也没水箱那么光线充足
Well,the truth is,we watch it for the drinking game.
我们看她节目其实是为了喝酒游戏
- *** - Her morning show comes on so early,
- 说得再明白些 - 她那个节目开播相当的早
we're usually still at the bar,
我们通常都还在酒吧呢
so whenever she does an interview,
因此 每当她访谈什么人
you have to drink every time she says,"But,um...
只要她说 "可 那个..."
- "But,um..."? - "But,um...
- "可 那个..."? - "可 那个..."
" Apparently,she says it a lot.
很明显 她说的相当频繁
It's funny. I had a drinking game based on Robin,but it was actually on Robin.
说来有趣 我也玩过和Robin相关的酒戏 只不过是真正的在她身上
- I'd pour peach schnapps in her belly button... - Dude,we agreed we wouldn't do this.
- 我先在她的肚脐上倒些桃子杜松子酒... - 哥们 不是说好不说这种事的吗
Sorry. You're right.
抱歉 你说的对
She didn't like it anyway. Said it woke her up.
再说她也不太喜欢 说老是弄醒她
Does she really say "But,um... " that much?
她真说"可 那个..."那么频繁吗?
That night,we found out just how much she said it.
那晚 我们知道了她说得有多频繁
- Oh,that's great. But,um... - But,um... Nice.
- 啊 真是太好了 可 那个... - 可那个... 好
this wasn't your first spelling bee,was it?
这不是你头一次参加拼字比赛吧?
Nope. Third.
不是 第三回了
Oh,good for you.
真是好孩子
But,um...
可 那个...
She's one of those people...
她原来是那种人...
Interesting article in the paper.
今天报纸上这文章还真有意思...
Says that in every relationship,there's a reacher and a settler.
说每对恋人中 都会有一人"高攀"一人"屈就"
Really? Let me see it.
是吗?哪呢 我看
No,uh,it's not in this newspaper. It's in one I read a while back.
没 不在这份报上 是我在早前的一份报上看的
This newspaper reminded me of the other newspaper.
这份报让我想起了那份报
Anywho...
不管怎么着吧...
what do you think about that?
你对这事怎么想?
Well,I guess sometimes that's the case.
嗯 有些恋人是那样的
But not in ours.
但咱们不是
What? No,of course not.
咱们当然不是
Right.
嗯
Well,say-- gun to your head--
不过 如果有把枪顶着你的头...
you had to say one of us was the reacher.
你被逼着非得说咱们中谁是高攀的
Well,I'd say it's neither.
那 我会说都不是
That's what makes us great.
所以咱们才这么融洽
Okay,now there's a gun tomyhead and our future children,
那 现在这枪指向了我的头 还有咱们的孩子
and our future cat or monkey,
还指着咱们将来养的猫或猴
depending on who wins the game of Risk we've been playing for three years.
至于是哪个 那得看咱们谁赢得了 未来三年的冒险游戏了
Nope. No reacher,no settler.
还是没有 没人高攀 没人屈就
- Well,how about this? - This went on for a while.
- 那这么说吧? - 这种车轱辘话说了大半晌
Until finally...
终于...
Our two kids,our eight grandkids,
我们的两个孩子 八个孙子
our 11 great-grandkids are all on a plane
11个重孙子 全都在一架飞机上
piloted by Oprah and it's about to crash into an art museum
Oprah驾驶着 马上就要撞上一家艺术博物馆
with all of your favorite paintings,and the only way...
里面全是你喜欢的作品 而唯一的出路...
the only way to save everything is just...
拯救这一切唯一的办法...
is just to answer the question:
就是回答下面这个问题
Are you the reacher or the settler?
你是"高攀"还是"屈就"
And Oprah's tried everything?
Oprah已经无计可施了?
Everything! You have to decide now.
没了 你必须当即立断
Well,I guess,if Ihadto say,then maybe I'd say I'm the settler.
那要是我非说不可的话 我得说我是"屈就"
How could you say that?!
你怎么能说出这种话来?
She thinks that she's the settler.
她说她是"屈就"于我了
I mean,that's it. I gotta-I gotta prove to her that I am not the reacher.
没法子了 我得向她证明我才不是"高攀"的
I gotta make her jealous.
我得让她吃醋
Well,that's easy. Here's the plan.
那简单 你就这么办
Step 1: Sleep with Jenkins.
第一步 和Jenkins上床
Step 2: I sleep with Jenkins first.
第二步 我先和Jenkins上床
Step 3: We do step two first.
第三步 咱们先实施第二步
I'm gonna go get started on step two.
我去执行第二步了
Okay,okay,I got something.
好吧 我有主意了
Remember the other night,the Skee-Ball game?
记不记得那晚玩滚球游戏?
When you were putting nothing but wood in the 50 hole?
你连连将木球投入50分洞口
Whatever. Just another night for Big Fudge.
有什么大不了的 只是我大软糖放异彩的又一晚而已
You thought she was into me?
你觉得她对我有意思?
Full-on lady wood.
简直为你着迷
Yes. Of course.
是啊 就是嘛
A plan taketh shape.
计划成形了
If Lady Lily's jealousy young Marshall cannot budge,
如果年轻的Marshall不能让淑女Lily吃醋
then perchance,fair gentles,Big Fudge...
那恐怕 先生们 大软糖...
can... make her jealous.
也许能...让她吃醋
- Okay,let me try that again. If Lady Lily's... - I got it,buddy. I got it.
- 这个不算 我再来一次 如果... - 我明白了 哥们 别说了
Ted,I have got a great idea.
Ted 我有了个绝妙的主意
Oh,is it "clean your hair "out of the shower drain when you're done"?
呃 你终于愿意洗完澡后 清理掉排水口上的头发了吗?
Seriously,it's like you're trying to carpet the tub.
没开玩笑 不知道的 还当你要给浴缸编个毯子呢
If you wanted to print out one of your lectures or something,
如果你愿意 你可以把你的讲议打印出来
I could read it on air.
我在节目中读一下
Coming from a more entertaining source,
通过这种寓教于乐的方式
your students might actually pay attention and learn something.
你的学生也许能真正的学到点东西
Oh,you're entertaing?
你那也叫寓教于乐?
Last night,there was three minutes of dead air
昨天你的节目有三分钟啥也没播
while you sewed a button back on your sweater.
就等着你把扣子重新缝回毛衣上
Look,just because your class likes me more than you...
听着 不能因为你的学生喜欢我多过你就...
- You're a drinking game! - What?
- 你不过是他们的酒戏 - 什么?
That's why they watch. They made a drinking game out of you.
他们看你的节目不过是想用你行个酒令
Every time you say "but,um... ," they do a shot.
只要你一说"可那个..." 他们就干一杯
- "But,um... "? - Yeah.
- "可 那个..."? - 是的
I don't say,"But,um... " I've never said,"But,um...
我才不说"可 那个..." 我从没说过"可那个..."
" Well,then,I guess it's not a very good drinking game.
那 我想 也许并不是啥好酒令
Which would mean last night,when Barney and I played it,
也就是说 昨天我和Barney行这个令时
I didn't get super wasted and throw up all over myself.
我没有喝到烂醉还吐了自己一身
Oh,wait,I did both of those things.
等下 我既醉且吐了
So,face.
直面现实吧
- Hey,Jenkins. - Hey,buddy.
- 嗨 Jenkins - 嗨 哥们
Hey,so,um,Lily and I are gonna go back to that college bar again.
嗨 呃 Lily和我还打算再去学校那间酒吧
And,uh,we were wondering if maybe you wanted to come.
我们想问问你去不去
Uh,you could just,like,watch me play Skee-Ball
呃 你可以去看我玩滚球
or do exactly what you did the other night. Something like that.
你就还像那天晚上那样表现 你明白那意思哈
It's really up to you. I mean,I know that...
当然 你自己决定 我是说 我知道...
Hey,baby,what are you doing home?
嗨 宝贝 怎么这么早就回来了
"Baby. " That's... that's a name I don't deserve.
"宝贝" 我配不上这个称呼了
- What? - Jenkins kissed me. She kissed me.
- 怎么了? - Jenkins 吻了我 她吻了我
The other day,she saw me play Skee-Ball,and I don't know,
那天 她一直在看我玩滚球 我也不知道
I guess she caught some of the Big Fudge fever.
我还觉得她可能是因为 大软糖一时头脑发热了
But you have to know I stopped it right away.
不过你要知道 我即刻制止了她
And just,you're the only one for me,baby.
而你 永远是我的唯一 宝贝
Oh,I see what this is.
我明白怎么回事了
This is about the whole reacher/settler thing.
你还在纠结高攀 屈就那回事呢
Come again for Big Fudge?
就为了大软糖再说一次?
You want to make me jealous,so you're making up a story about Jenkins.
你想让我吃醋 所以你就编了和Jenkins的瞎话
I'm not making this up! This happened.
我没编瞎话 确有其事
That woman kissed me with tongue.
那娘们舌头都用上了
Her-her tongue was in my mouth.
她的舌头都进了我的嘴里了
Sure it was.
对 进了
It was thick and rough like a starfish arm.
她的舌头又厚又粗糙 好像海星的触角
Oh,I'm so jealous.
真是气死了我
I'm just gonna go over there and punch her right in the nose.
我要去你们公司 打她个春光灿烂
Give her a knuckle sandwich.
对她饱以老拳
Come on,baby. You want some soup?
好了 宝贝 要喝汤吗?
It happened!
确有其事啊
Do you have any...
你有没有...
split pea left?
留点豆子给我?
These are just a few of the many contributions he made to architecture
这些只是他对建筑界所做贡献的一角
and yet he is only rembered for one thing.
然而他只因一件作品为人们所铬记
That my friends,is the sad legacy of Gregorio Franchetti Gazebo.
同学们 那就是令人难过的 Gregorio Franchetti Gazebo
Any questions?
有问题吗?
- Hey,do you want to go out drinking with us tonight? - What?
- 今晚你要不要和我们一起去喝一杯 - 什么?
Yeah,we're gonna play the Robin Scherbatsky drinking game.
我们还要行那个Robin Scherbatsky酒令
We were wondering if you wanted to join us.
想知道你能不能一起来
Well,what can I say except "But,ums up.
那 我只能说 一起"可那个"吧
" Can I still come? I'll pay.
还带我吧? 我买单
- Nice. - Oh,yeah.
- 很好 - 哦耶
So,your third book was your breakout novel but,um...
这么说你第三本小说才开始崭露头角 可那个...
But,um...!
可那个!
Damn! Sorry.
靠 对不起
But-- just "but" no "um," just "but.
可-只有"可" 没"那个" 只有 "可"
" Your first novel was written more quickly.
你的第一部小说写得更快些
That's correct.
是的
- But,um... - But,um...
- 可 那个... - 可 那个...
How great is this?
真是太爽了
And it was right then that Robin got an idea
然而 就在那时 Robin有了主意
that would end the drinking game forever.
一个能永远结束这酒戏的主意
I wanted to ask you about the novel you're writing right now.
我想问下您现下正在写的这部小说
- But,um... - But,um...
- 可 那个... - 可 那个...
... it's an idea you've had for a,but,um...
灵感来自于你 那个...
But,um...
可 那个
- ... long time,but,um... - But,um...
- 长期的 可那个... - 可 那个...
No... No,no,no. Don't drink,it's a trap!
停 停 停 别喝了 这是个陷阱
I think I'm gonna go. You can keep your ten bucks.
我得走了 那十块钱你留着自个花吧
Okay,but,um,thanks for being with us.
好啊 可 那个 感谢你能来
But,um,if there's any college kids watching,
可 那个 如果有大学生在看本节目
but,um,but,um,but,um,but,um,but,um,but,um,but,um,but,um...
可 那个... 可那个... 可那个 ....
We have to drink,Professor. It's the rules.
咱们不得不喝 教授 这是规则
She said,"But,um...
只要她说 "可 那个..."
God help us all.
主啊 救救我们
Here you are.
你在这呢
- I'm so sorry I kissed you yesterday. - That's okay.
- 真抱歉昨天吻了你 - 没关系
- And I'm sorry I had sex with you in the mailroom. - That wasn't me.
- 也为昨天和你在收发室的嘿咻抱歉 - 那人不是我
Oh,good grief,that's two awkward conversations I have to have today.
这下好了  今天得有两次尴尬的谈话了
I don't normally do that. I-I was really drunk.
我平常不是这个样子的 当时醉得太厉害了
You were drunk at 8:00 in the morning?
你早上8点还没醒酒呢?
Yeah,I don't know how that happened.
是呀 我也不知道咋搞的
I thought snail pellets were safe,but,um...
我个人觉得蜗牛丸子很安全 可 那个...
But,um...
可 那个...
I gotta get to work.
我得上班去了
Man,that game is really catching on.
老天 这游戏还挺流行
Damn it,how could I do this?
真是的 我怎么会做这种事
It's okay.
没事的
No,you know what,it's not okay.
不 当然有事
You're the nicest guy in this stupid office
这烂办公室里 你是最好的人了
and I really don't want to screw up our friendship.
我真的不想破坏咱们 纯洁的男女关系
This is so embarrassing. Please don't tell anyone.
真是太丢人了 请不要和别人讲
No,who am I gonna tell? Lily? I told Lily.
当然不会 我能告诉谁呀? 我告诉Lily了
Oh,for Pete's sake,well,I gotta go talk to her. I gotta apologize.
老天啊 我只好去和她谈谈了 我得去道歉
- No! No! Don't... - Yes. Marshall,I'm just gonna tell her that it happened,
- 不用 不用 不要... - 要的 Marshall 我得向她坦白 确有其事啊
that it meant nothing and that I'm sorry.
不过那完全不意味着任何事情 我很抱歉
No,I...
不 我...
- Yes. Yes. Do that. - I will.
- 对 对 去吧 - 我会的
Yeah,and if you don't have time for all that,
对 要是你赶时间
just tell her it happened,and that you're sorry.
只要和她说确有其事 你很抱歉就行了
And if you're in a real rush,you don't even have to say,"I'm sorry.
要是时间真的很紧 道歉就省了吧
" Just tell her that it happened.
只要说确有其事就行了
That's the important part,that it actually happened.
这才是重点 确确实实有其事
So emphasize that as much as you can.
尽可能的多强调这一点
And so,Lily,I guess what I'm saying is,it happened.
因此 Lily 我得说 确有其事
I feel terrible about it,and I'm really sorry.
我真的非常抱歉
aaa
唉 确有其事呀
bbb
我有什么办法 真的发生了
ccc
很可怕 可确有其事
ddd
是呀 我也很内疚 我都恨我自己
eee
我的所做伤害了你 还有你和Marshall的关系
fff
请你一定要原谅我
ggg
敢亲我老公 我的老公 除了我 谁也不能亲我孩他爹
hhh
Marshall 你挡住镜头了
- iii - jjj
- 孩子们 你们的Marshall叔叔再也没敢   让你Lily阿姨吃醋 - 这才带劲
kkk
今儿这节课咱们都低调点
lll
不准说话
mmm
不准制造噪音
nnn
你们还好吧 大家伙
ooo
不 不 不 走远点
ppp
我就是顺道来说一句
qqq
感谢收看"早安纽约"
rrr
可 那个...